{
    "subject": "resource/Henry_Cuellar",
    "predicate": "ontology/residence",
    "object": "resource/Texas",
    "human_readable": "Henry Cuellar resides in Texas.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.96978360414505,
            "question": "Is Henry Cuellar a resident of Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9688965082168579,
            "question": "Is Texas the location of Henry Cuellar's residence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8796030282974243,
            "question": "Where does Henry Cuellar live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8551713228225708,
            "question": "In which US state does Henry Cuellar reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8325300812721252,
            "question": "Where is Henry Cuellar currently located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.629254937171936,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Henry Cuellar's place of residence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6067304015159607,
            "question": "What state is Henry Cuellar from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5800328254699707,
            "question": "What is the name of the state where Henry Cuellar lives?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4388945996761322,
            "question": "To what state is Henry Cuellar connected?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2889004051685333,
            "question": "What is the state that Henry Cuellar calls home?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Henry Cuellar resides in Texas.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3351_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what state is Henry Cuellar connected?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3351_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the state where Henry Cuellar lives?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3351_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is Henry Cuellar from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3351_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3351_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3351_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3351_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3351_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3351_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3351_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3351_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3351_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3351_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3351_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Henry Cuellar resides in Texas\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents provide multiple mentions of Henry Cuellar being associated with Texas, including his birthplace (Laredo, Texas), his legislative district (Texas' 28th congressional district), and his residence (Laredo, Texas)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Congressman Henry Cuellar is from Laredo, Texas, and serves in the U.S. House of Representatives representing Texas\u2019 28th congressional district. This supports the statement that Henry Cuellar resides in Texas."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}